It's a Rom-Zom-Com!
Night of the Living Deb is a comedy, horror film directed by Kyle Rankin.
After a one night stand Deb wakes up in the middle of a zombie apocalypse.
Deb Clarington, played by Maria Thayer.
Ryan Waverly, played by Michael Cassidy.
Frank Waverly, played by Ray Wise.
Chaz Waverly, played by Christopher Rodriguez Marquette.
Stacy, played by Syd Wilder.
Ruby, played by Julie Brister.
Night of the Living Deb is a 2015 American romantic
zombie comedy film directed by Kyle Rankin.
It stars Maria Thayer, Michael Cassidy, Ray Wise and Chris Marquette.
Thayer plays an awkward woman who, after a one-night stand,
realizes she has awoken to a zombie apocalypse.
The film explores themes of maine, spoof, zombie, cannibal, fourth of july.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.